

As for my abilities, I have good analytical skills and strong leadership. As a person, I am a hard worker, honest, quick learner, cooperative, full with enthusiasm and strong motivator. I believe that my knowledge and experience will be potential asset for your company.

## **EDUCATION**

Information Technology State University of Surabaya 3.29/4 GPA

## **INTERNSHIPS**

Internship at PT Semen Gresik (Persero) Tbk (2005)

## **LANGUAGES**

• Indonesian

English

# CATUR PAMUNGKAS

## SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER**

DAILY VANITY PTE LTD | NOV. 2020 - NOV. 2022 **SINGAPORE** 

#### Job responsibilities:

- Develop maintainable and reusable code using OOP methodologies
- Practice Test Driven Development
- Front End development with Angular & React
- Build REST API to support front end applications
- Identify ways to enhance the user experience
- Built WordPress Themes & Plugins
- Basic support for internal IT related issues
- Improve existing system or process

## Language & Stack:

- PHP
- WordPress
- HTML
- Angular
- ReactJS
- CSS / SCSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- TypeORM
- NodeJS

- Webpack
- jQuery
- **AJAX**
- GitHub
- MySQL
- Linux
- Apache
- Nginx
- **AWS**
- REST API

#### **BACK END PROGRAMMING MANAGER**

PT EXCITE INDONESIA | OCT. 2016 - OCT. 2020 JAKARTA, INDONESIA

#### Job responsibilities:

Lead back end web developers to develop, maintain, and support Excite applications from Reward Point System, Loyalty Network Service, Redemption Operation, Partner Analytics to Excite Shop, Affiliate Marketing System and Blog websites Reporting to the Head of Engineering Daily communication with various team, outside partners

clients and others, for direction, strategy, and priority

## Language & Stack:

- PHP
- Framework BEAR
- Framework Laravel
- Framework Lumen
- Framework Phalcon
- Git, SVN
- MySQL
- WordPress

- HTML
- CSS/SCSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- AJAX
- REST API

## **SKILLS**

- PHP
- Codelgniter
- Laravel
- Lumen
- WordPress
- ASP
- Python
- GoLang
- Visual Basic
- Crystal Reports
- HTML/HTML5
- CSS/CSS3
- SCSS/SASS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- **Typescript**
- TypeORM
- ¡Query
- AJAX
- JSON
- NodeJS
- PM2
- Webpack
- Vue.js

- Angular
- React
- Material UI
- REST API
- Git
- SVN
- Photoshop
- Figma
- Windows Server
- IIS
- Nginx
- Ubuntu
- Agile
- Scrum
- Sprint
- Jira
- Trello
- Freshdesk
- SQL Server
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- Firebase

## CONTACT

Address: Kebagusan City Apartment, Jakarta, Indonesia 12520

Phone: +628563061982

Email: chesspamungkas@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/catur-pamungkas/

Website: https://chesspamungkas.com

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

APR. 2015 - OCT. 2016 JAKARTA, INDONESIA

## Job responsibilities:

Worked in coordination with clients to sort out their technical issues and determine the client's goals and expectations for their website.

#### Language & Stack:

- PHP
- Framework Codelgniter
- Framework Laravel
- MySQL
- WordPress
- HTML
- CSS / SCSS

- Bootstrap JavaScript
- ¡Query
- AJAX
- Photoshop
- · Web Hosting

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

PT SUPRA PRIMATAMA NUSANTARA (BIZNET NETWORKS) | JAN. 2008 - MAR. 2015 JAKARTA, INDONESIA

## Job responsibilities:

Built and develop a database system, develop Biznet Networks website, coverage area system, online sales league dashboard system, online sales incentive dashboard system, online employee overtime system, online leave management system, built newsletter system at Bank BCA, assist website project at Microsoft Indonesia.

## Language & Stack:

- ASP
- PHP
- SQL Server
- IIS
- SAP Business One
- Bootstrap
- CSS / CSS3
- JavaScript
- Windows Server

## **IT PROGRAMMER**

INTERNATIONAL AIR TRANSPORT ASSOCIATION (IATA) NOV. 2006 - JAN. 2008 JAKARTA, INDONESIA

#### Job responsibilities:

Develop desktop applications for internal.

## Language & Stack:

- Visual Basic 6
- Crystal Reports
- SQL Server
- Microsoft Excel VBA

## **PROGRAMMER**

PT ROTASIS INDONESIA | FEB. 2006 - NOV. 2006 JAKARTA, INDONESIA

#### Job responsibilities:

Develop desktop applications to the needs of the client, including applications for hospitals and travel agents.

## Language & Stack:

- Visual Basic 6
- Crystal Reports
- MySQL